<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<catalog>
  <item>
    <id>1</id>
    <title>Gourd-shaped vase with Indian lotus decoration in wucai painted enamels</title>
    <author>Unknown</author>
    <period>Ming Dynasty, Jiajing period</period>
    <type>Porcelain</type>
    <description>The 'passionflower' is an exotic botanical motif derived from a hybrid design combining Indian lotus and Persian floral elements. The pattern layout features symmetrical floral motifs, clearly influenced by Islamic decorative art.</description>
    <image>1500guo 1stpic.png</image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>2</id>
    <title>Blue-and-white dish with floral cartouche and bird design</title>
    <author>Unknown</author>
    <period>Ming Dynasty, Wanli period</period>
    <type>Porcelain</type>
    <description>The dish has a flared rim, shallow sides, a sunken center, and a ring foot. It is fully decorated in underglaze blue. In the center is a design of flowers and birds.</description>
    <image>xinyi2.png</image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>3</id>
    <title>Bowl with "presenting the treasure" motif in doucai painted enamels</title>
    <author>Unknown</author>
    <period>Ming Dynasty, Wanli period</period>
    <type>Porcelain</type>
    <description>Decorated in the typical Ming-dynasty doucai technique, this piece features bright, richly layered colors. The exterior is adorned with auspicious 'Jinbao' motifs.</description>
    <image>xinyi3.png</image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>4</id>
    <title>Bowl decorated with flowers of the four seasons in yangcai painted enamels</title>
    <author>Unknown</author>
    <period>Qing Dynasty, Yongzheng period</period>
    <type>Porcelain</type>
    <description>The exterior is adorned with multicolored floral designs, including peonies, peony-rose, chrysanthemums, and other blossoms; both the flowers and foliage are outlined in red and black enamels.</description>
    <image>xinyi4.png</image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>5</id>
    <title>Tea bowl with floral scroll on a black ground in falangcai painted enamels</title>
    <author>Unknown</author>
    <period>Qing Dynasty, Qianlong period</period>
    <type>Porcelain</type>
    <description>The exterior features a black ground with enamel-painted peonies, exotic lotuses, and other entwined seasonal flowers as the main motifs.</description>
    <image>xinyi5.png</image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>6</id>
    <title>Vase with figure, flower and bird decoration in yangcai painted enamels</title>
    <author>Unknown</author>
    <period>Qing Dynasty, Qianlong period</period>
    <type>Porcelain</type>
    <description>Polychrome decoration depicts sloping ground with light grasses, peach and willow trees with spring swallows, and a farmer with a child herding animals.</description>
    <image>xinyi6.png</image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>7</id>
    <title>Underglaze-blue porcelain snuff bottle with a landscape-and-figure design</title>
    <author>Unknown</author>
    <period>Qing Dynasty (1900s)</period>
    <type>Porcelain</type>
    <description>Bottle-shaped, with a straight mouth, short neck, cylindrical body. Features a blue-and-white depiction of a man fishing beneath a pine tree before a cliff.</description>
    <image>yuming1.png</image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>8</id>
    <title>Bencharong Covered Bowl (Lai Nam Thong style)</title>
    <author>Unknown</author>
    <period>Qing Dynasty (1900s)</period>
    <type>Porcelain / Export Ware</type>
    <description>Porcelain covered bowl decorated in the Lai Nam Thong style of Chinese export ware made for the Thai market. Painted with enamel colours: turquoise, red and gold.</description>
    <image>yuming2.png</image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>9</id>
    <title>Yellow-Ground Famille Rose Rectangular Planter with Lotus Designs</title>
    <author>Unknown</author>
    <period>Late 19th Century, Qing Dynasty</period>
    <type>Porcelain</type>
    <description>Rectangular planter with a flat mouth. The exterior features famille rose decoration on a pale yellow ground. The four sides depict a continuous lotus pond scene.</description>
    <image>yuming3.png</image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>10</id>
    <title>Flambé Glazed Apricot Medallion Vase</title>
    <author>Unknown</author>
    <period>Late 19th Century, Qing Dynasty</period>
    <type>Porcelain</type>
    <description>Rectangular vase with symmetrical tubular handles. Covered overall in flambé glaze. The late Qing flambé glazes were predominantly red with intermingling black patches.</description>
    <image>yuming4.png</image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>11</id>
    <title>Famille Rose Vase Depicting Mulan's Homecoming</title>
    <author>Wang Dafan</author>
    <period>Republic of China Period</period>
    <type>Porcelain</type>
    <description>Painted using traditional overglaze enamels. The scene vividly depicts Mulan's triumphant return and her family's joy, derived from the 'Ballad of Mulan'.</description>
    <image>yuming5.png</image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>12</id>
    <title>China-Albania Friendship Porcelain Sculpture</title>
    <author>Unknown</author>
    <period>Cultural Revolution Era</period>
    <type>Porcelain Sculpture</type>
    <description>Sculpted using traditional round carving techniques. It depicts Chinese and Albanian youths holding the 'Little Red Book' and singing praises.</description>
    <image>yuming6.png</image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>13</id>
    <title>Five Storey's: Chinese Ladders 3</title>
    <author>Felicity Aylieff</author>
    <period>2009</period>
    <type>Porcelain Sculpture</type>
    <description>Monumental blue-and-white porcelain sculpture created in collaboration with Jingdezhen 'Big Ware' master potters.</description>
    <image>yutong1.png</image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>14</id>
    <title>Narrative Ceramics Installation (GIRINO / IL CANTANTE...)</title>
    <author>ELICA Studio</author>
    <period>2009</period>
    <type>Porcelain Installation</type>
    <description>Four-piece porcelain installation blending Italian 'istoriato' narrative ceramics with contemporary Jingdezhen exchanges.</description>
    <image>yutong2.png</image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>15</id>
    <title>Nine Cranes Dancing</title>
    <author>Ma Jun</author>
    <period>1994</period>
    <type>Thin-body Porcelain</type>
    <description>Record-breaking thin-body porcelain bowl created using 'fen shui' (water separation) and semi-carving techniques.</description>
    <image>yutong3.png</image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>16</id>
    <title>'March' - Porcelain - Physical NFT</title>
    <author>Wang Wei Ping</author>
    <period>2004 / Minted later</period>
    <type>Porcelain + NFT</type>
    <description>Jingdezhen porcelain vessel later minted as a Physical NFT on ArtAreas.io; connected to the digital token through an NFC chip.</description>
    <image>yutong4.mp4</image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>17</id>
    <title>Weapons of Choice</title>
    <author>FuturePunk</author>
    <period>2020</period>
    <type>Digital Artwork</type>
    <description>A digital artwork rendering weapons using ceramic-like textures and reflective digital surfaces.</description>
    <image>yutong5.png</image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>18</id>
    <title>Hermes</title>
    <author>Uwe Heine Debrodt</author>
    <period>2021</period>
    <type>Digital GIF / NFT</type>
    <description>Physical Raku-fired sculpture transformed into a digital animated NFT through 3D scanning.</description>
    <image>yutong6.mp4</image>
  </item>
</catalog>
